Troy Sirat

(702) 420-3515 — swimdude96@yahoo.com Las Vegas, NV 89110

Short Bio

Raised in Las Vegas, I'm a 18 year old Senior at Southwest Career and Tech Academy. I enjoy being mentored and learning about almost anything. Audio, video, and code are my passions.

Skills

Musically Inclined Time Management Multitasking Organization Public Speaking

Experience

Web Based Project Design (September 2011 - Present)

1 1/2+ years' experience studying in collaborative learning environment. Participating in teams with various roles like team leader, assistant, etc.

Clark County Life Guard (June 2012 - August 2012)

Practiced saving lives daily and enjoying the experience.

State Skills USA Winner (2013)

Competed and placed first in the competitive event of Community Service and absolutely gained more than imagined from working on the project.

State Skills USA Second Place Winner (2014)

Competed and placed second in the competitive event of Community Service and enjoyed participating in this event for a second time.

State FCCLA First Place Winner (2014)

Competed and placed first in the competitive event of Chapter Website.

National FCCLA First Place Winner (2014)

Competed and placed first in the competitive event of Chapter Website. The abilities that my partner Jay and I learned in web design and development helped us to win this competition.

Education

Southwest Career and Technical Academy 2011 - present Major: Web Design | Minor: Broadcast

Organizations

DECA | 2011 - 2013 SkillsUSA | 2012 - Present FCCLA | 2013 - Present

Community Service

Girls In Technology: Video Production Team Member | Spring 2013

Colour Run | Spring 2013

Gay Haven: Services Member | 2009 - Present

